Vikrant Singh Bhadouriya

I. T. Analyst

A competent engineer with 4.7 years of IT experience, including development of end-to-end automation, production support, structuring, managing and platform assistance in the creation of RPA (Robotics Process Automation) solutions using UiPath. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving client satisfaction. Looking for a challenging role in an organization where I can use my current knowledge for quality delivery and expand my learning and up skill myself with new opportunity.

xikrantsv10@gmail.com



8982174185



Noida, India

in linkedin.com/in/vikrantbhadouriya

WORK EXPERIENCE

RPA Support Lead

Tata Consultancy Services Ltd.

09/2022 - Present

Noida, Uttar Pradesh

CISCO

- Managing offshore team of five members for project execution and delivery.
- Upgraded the UiPath studio and Orchestrator from v2019 to 2022.
- Engaged in setting up BIZ's Automation Suite for usage with AI Center and Document Understanding.
- Facilitated SSL certificate renewal process and seamlessly linked it to the production orchestrator, ensuring uninterrupted system security.
- Constant communication with business teams to develop and deploy their ideas. Also, make sure that there is a clear understanding of what can be created in what timeframe and what its requirements are.
- Utilized JIRA and ServiceNow for efficient defect tracking and streamlined communication with developers to expedite issue resolution.
- Provided ongoing operational support, including upgrades, defect fixes, and process change activities, to ensure system stability and performance.
- Experience in providing functional and KT sessions to support team for effective production.

RPA Developer

Tata Consultancy Services Ltd.

08/2019 - 08/2022

Nagpur, Maharashtra

DOCS-Diligenta Output and Correspondance System

- Developed and deployed end to end 2 automated solutions/Bots which include a combination of database and SharePoint automation.
- Well experienced in Production Deployment and Post Deployment Support with good scholar in Orchestrator functionalities involving in complete code movement along each phase.
- Experience in working with relational data base management
- Expertise on exception handling.

EDUCATION

B.Tech: Computer Science and Engineering Amity University Madhya Pradesh

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Star Team Award

Was awarded for proactive working and code review to check if the code adheres to the coding standards of client and for best logic applicable.

Best Team Award

Was awarded 2 times in the organization for critical deliveries.

On the Spot Award

Was awarded 2 times for taking the responsibility at some emergency requirement.

Special Initiative Award

Automated numerous routine tasks using UiPath thereby reducing manual intervention and handle time.

Certificate of Appreciation

Was appreciated 2 times for full support in Urgent deliveries in TCS.

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

French

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Exploring new places

Photography

Volunteering

Playing Chess